I... I...
...I'm late!
Let's chase our dreams...
... holding hearts burning...
... like the summer sunshine.
If we have courage...
... at 100 miles an hour...
... I'm sure the door will open.
Since sadness is the road
that leads to smiles...
... dull, dingy shoes will
start to shine, too.
The most wonderful dream
in the world...
The pounding beat speeds up.
The eyes are prisms that
catch the wind...
... and in the voices of
countless friends...
... I feel happiness.
LOVE'S HIGHWAY STARS
Ladies' Locker Room
Good morning!
Yoriko! Good morning!
Miyuki! Good morning!
Good morning.
Oh? Where's Natsumi?
Sleeping late, as usual.
You didn't wake her up?
You're living together.
I tried! Ice packs, firecrackers,
BB guns, headphone blasts...
...every day her immunity to wakeups
gets stronger and stronger.
So, I've decided to leave
her alone from now on.
We got days off this weekend, didn't we?
What's with these red marks?
Huh? OH!
Sorry! I couldn't help
seeing them!
What's today?
Huh? It's Thursday.
I completely forgot about replying!
What should I do?!
Weekend? "Reply?"
This is fishy!
There! I made it! No
thanks to Miyuki!
Natsumi! Good morning!
Oh... Morning!
What's with that laugh? A-ha! I bet
you're onto something juicy again!
Wanna know?
I heard that Yoriko saw the evidence!
That poor Nakajima!
You think Miyuki hears her clock ticking?
Wouldn't you want to try it, even once?
Try what once?
Oh come on, you know what!
You mean Nakajima wasn't #1 on her list?
I never thought that this would happen!
Good mornin'! Huh? What the?
What's with those faces?!
Nakajima, I've got something to talk to
you about. Come with me for a sec.
Huh?!
Kennie!
Come with me!
Ugh! Lemme go!
Shut up!
An "Omiai?!" But you don't
know that for sure, right?
This is no time to act
so laid back!
A weekend meeting that
requires an RSVP...
Can it be anything other than a formal
Omiai matchmaking introduction?
See! It's all your fault for not telling
her how you really feel about her!
Whatcha gonna do now?!
This means... you're gonna have
to kidnap her... or else!
K... Kidnap her?!
Don't you care if some guy
steals her away?!
Take her away?! You're blowing
this out of proportion...
You've got to make sure that she
doesn't make it to that meeting!
What do you mean by that?
Hey! Nakajima! Are you a man or what?!
Why can't you be a little more
direct for a change?!
Right! If you're a man, then go after
her until you get her or drop dead!
Now, now...
"Would you like to go out touring,
Ms. Kobayakawa?"
No, using "Ms." is weird! Hmm...
"Let's go out touring!"
If I'm asking her out, then I'd
better not sound so snooty!
"Why don't we go touring!
Huh? Huh?"
Ehh... Now that'll make me look like
an idiot! Maybe I should just ask...
What's wrong, Nakajima?
Well, umm... HUH?!
Why, that's...
Like it? It's Natsumi's...
Tsujimoto's?!
Yeah.
She got so excited after I put the chamber
and aluminum swing-arm on it...
...that she ended up
driving it all night.
But... I thought she wasn't
much of a motorhead...
Well, she sure can tell when something's
changed... She can be rather picky!
Oh, well, actually I wanted you to
check something out for me...
What is it? As long as you don't
need it done right away...
No, it can wait. I don't mind!
I do!
There's no time to get excited
over bikes, am I right?!
You know well that I've told you to go
to bed early many, many times!
We're 15 minutes
late for patrol!
That's not it! What are you
waiting for?! C'mon!
Er... er... Well... Would
you like to?
What's with you two?!
You see, Nakajima here...
...is trying to keep you from your Omiai,
and is therefore asking you for a date!
Er... er... well...
He asks, "Are you free
this weekend?"
Weekend? This weekend?
Y... Yeah!
Sorry, I have to do something
this weekend... So I can't.
But, wait a minute here... Who said
anything about an Omiai?
Huh?! B... But... Even Natsumi said she
had no idea about your plans, so that...
Yoriko!
Ah... Er... Well!
Oh, I don't know about this... Maybe
I'll just come home tonight.
Gee, it's your reunion, isn't it?!
Don't worry about a thing,
and just go have fun.
But, if I'm away, who knows what kind
of rumors about me will circulate?!
Don't get Nakajima mixed up
in anything, okay?
Are you worried about him?
That's NOT what I mean...
Okay, okay... Get going!
You'll be late!
If you see any cool classmates,
point them in my direction!
Well, then, I'm going.
Take care... Okay?
Have a good trip!
A-ha, she went to
a co-ed school...
Nakajima, are you here?
Oh, my! Lookin' miserable!
What's goin' on?
It wasn't an Omiai, so what're
you worried about?!
Gee... Look, Nakajima, we all know
that you're weak sometimes...
...that when the going gets tough,
you don't get going...
...that you got no guts, are slow, and a
sissy. But, what can you do now?
You can't fight fate,
you know...
H... Hey! This
ain't helping!
At times like this, you've got to
release all that pent-up stress!
And I know just the
place to do that!
What the?
Oh, c'mon!
That poor ZXR wants you
to take her out for a ride!
Get your butt moving, dude!
You're in our way!
Oh, brother...
Here goes!
You maniac! You tryin' to
kill me or something?!
Nah, I'm reviving you!
I hope that I'll get a commendation
from the Captain for my work...
...I hope that I can keep on talking
to Tokuno every day...
...I hope my lunch-making
skills improve...
...I hope for more samurai
drama re-runs...
...and I hope the summer will be
blessed with good weather...
Okay, let's go buy some
lucky charms!
A lucky charm? What,
for "traffic safety?"
No, for a closer relationship
between you two!
Like the God of Love says,
"Love Shall Flourish!"
Give it to Miyuki, and I'm sure
it'll work out for both of you!
Er... No... I don't wanna
be so blunt!
Don't try to squirm out of this!
It's not the "buying," it's the "giving..."
Oh, really?
So, that's how you
want it, eh?
"Hotel Taihei Inn"
Kimizu High School
Reunion
Gee, long time no see!
Miyuki?! You're looking good!
Yeah! A grown-up woman!
You all look different!
I'm speechless!
Hey, Miyuki, you're a cop
now, right? Awesome!
Do you get involved in shootouts?
No, not really...
Do you get in fights with crooks?
No way!
Do you carry handcuffs and stuff?
W... Well, yeah...
Miyuki went to a co-ed
high school...
...that means, today's reunion...
will also feature men!
First time since graduation, eh?
Well, have some!
Thanks, Kido...
I wonder... if an old boyfriend
might show up or something!
Wanna step out with
me for a while?
Huh? Kido...
That... I can't abide!
And yet...
You don't mind if Miyuki's old
boyfriend grabs her?!
I DO mind!
Then act! What're you waiting for?!
Taihei Inn, in Katsuura...
Here we come!
It's kind of embarrassing in
front of everyone, isn't it?
Why... now?
I wanted to settle things,
once and for all...
You're slow! A fly
is resting on you!
Shut up, you turtle!
It's all in the past. I've tried
to forget all about it.
Why don't we just forget
that it ever happened?
We can't do that!
Even if you were to forget about it,
it'd always be on my mind...
This is more like it!
Here... The lunch money
you lent me 3 years ago!
At last, I've paid you back!
Boy, it feels good!
Gosh... You haven't
changed at all!
I can never tell whether
you're serious or not!
"Taihei Inn"
I'm sorry, but we don't have
a guest by that name.
This IS the Taihei Inn, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
This IS Katsuura City, isn't it?
Er, well... Is there another
Taihei Inn in Katsuura?
We're the only one.
Oh! I know! It's in Chiba!
Katsuura City... in CHIBA
Prefecture!
N... No way...
Oh! He's dead.
Well, so what's
the story?
What do you mean?
You know... your guy. What's he like?
Is he tall? Out with it!
What's going on? What are
you talking about?
Get this! Satomi is dating
someone from work!
Wow...
I wanted to go out with someone from a
different walk of life, but... I fell for him.
Yeah, that happens!
So, it seems I didn't
need to look far.
It'd be nice for a prince to arrive on
a white stallion, but even so...
Exactly! It's not like I asked
for it, but he came for me!
What do you mean by that, when
you're all blushed up!
We know about being happily in love...
it's written all over your face!
Oh, stop it!
Didn't need to look far, huh?
Look at you, Miyuki! What's
the meaning of that sigh?
Let me guess!
It's nothing!
Who is he?
What?!
Just like I thought!
No! No! It's not like that at all!
Admit it!
What's he like?
There's no one!
No one!
Besides, I'm just barely
keeping up at work...
There's no time to date a guy or anything
like that... realistically speaking!
Married to your work, eh? You sure
haven't changed at all, Miyuki.
You've always been
that way.
Yeah. It was like, you weren't
interested in guys at all!
Instead, you talked about your
hobbies all the time!
You were actually popular
with the guys, you know?
So I was always thinking,
"Damn! What a waste!"
Miyuki wasn't interested in that, 'cause
she had goals. Right, Miyuki?
I didn't have any ambitions
like that...
All I thought was, "It'd be nice
if I could get married early."
Maybe you expect too much
from life, Miyuki.
I bet you're waiting for someone who's
tall, totally athletic, kind, sweet...
...went to a top school, and makes
the big bucks. Am I right?
W... Well, something
like that...
That'd be a sight to see! I wonder what
Miyuki's significant other will be like?!
Look, Nakajima, everyone screws up now
and then. Besides, you're from Suzuka...
...so you wouldn't know about
the two Katsuura's!
Well, it was partly my fault for not
realizing it along the way, but...
Guess we got carried away with
the drivin', you know!
So I'm a wimp...
...who's weak, and can't take the pressure
when the going gets tough.
I got no guts, I'm slow,
I'm a sissy...
And on top of that, I'm also a klutz, an
oaf, and a dimwit... I'm hopeless!
Nakajima! Pathetic!
You're pathetic!
T... Tsujimoto!
I'll cheer you up!
W... Wait a sec, Tsujimoto!
Drink up and sing out in joy!
Go for it, Nakajima!
Eyaah! Knock it off, Tsujimoto!
We won't be able to go home!
Let's booze it 'til daybreak!
S... Somebody, save me!
You're not going anywhere!
We'll get busted for DWI!
Go for another bottle!
Phew! You reek of Sake!
Katsuura Station
Well, I better get going
from here...
I was hoping that we could go to
an aquarium or something.
Too bad. Maybe next time, okay?
Next time, I'll introduce
you to my boyfriend!
At the very least... he's tall.
My! This is yesterday's
evening paper!
If she was going out, Natsumi could've
at least put it inside the apartment!
Miyuki... Is Nakajima home?
N... No. It seems
like he's out.
How could he go out in
this kinda weather?!
I just don't understand this
bike riding thing at all!
Well, I notice that you're also
out and about, Yoriko!
Yeah, well, I have a legitimate
excuse... souvenirs!
I'm like a rat in a trap, eh? Well, make
sure everyone gets a share, okay?
These are those famous
Peanut Rice-Cakes!
I know! Though, I wonder where
Natsumi or Nakajima are...
Well, speak of the devil,
here's Nakajima now...
...and Natsumi?!
C... Coming home
in the morning?!
And? So, what happened?
Well, Nakajima and Tsujimoto went
out touring, and stayed overnight!
While Kobayakawa was out, right?
Is he flirting or something?
Well, I guess that's what
it boils down to.
Hey, don't go around spreading
unsubstantiated rumors.
Y... Yes, sir... Sorry
about that, sir!
The way I heard it, Nakajima's heart
was broken, and he just snapped...
...and asked Tsujimoto out.
Ah...
Allow me to explain...
if you would!
Ummm... Ahem! Er... Miyuki?
Got a minute?
It's okay.
Huh?
I know all about it. You were just trying
to cheer Nakajima up, right?
W... Well... something like that.
Don't worry about it. Rumors
don't mean anything...
Oh! Miyuki, it's full!
Oh! Oh, my! Let me see here...
A rag! Where's a rag?!
Health Checkup
Take Good Care
of Your Teeth
I heard that you fell.
Y... Yeah. I think it has
to do with this fever...
Fever?! You have a cold
or something?
Uh... it's nothing much. I'm just a
little under the weather, I think...
Oh... Oh, yeah! Thanks
for the tasty souvenir!
I got them for everyone...
I got something for y-
I gotta get going now. Sorry...
I got something
for you, too...
She said not to worry about it, but I'm sure
she's lying. She looked so upset!
I mean, it's weird NOT
to worry about it.
You just had to say something that was
totally uncalled for, didn't you?!
Natsumi... don't be cruel!
Up 'til now, no matter how upset she was,
she never avoided me like this...
This is serious...
Good grief! I can't take
this anymore!
Wait, Tsujimoto! Where
are you going?!
Someplace nice!
Miyuki!
Nakajima wants
to talk to you!
Go on, tell her how
you really feel!
W... What?! Who, me?!
Come on! Tell her, like a
real man should! Do it!
B... But...
Why you!
Nakajima! Go for it!
Everyone's rooting for you! Now pluck up
your courage, and tell her how you feel!
Nakajima, go for it!
Yeah! Show her what you're made of!
Do it, Nakajima!
Yoriko... you're at it again!
But!
Miyuki, sorry... I didn't mean for
something like this to happen...
You're SO insensitive!
Leave me alone for
a while! Please?
Chief, here are today's reports, sir.
Please look through them.
This many?!
There's more, sir.
Urk!
Natsumi, it's time
to go on patrol.
Oh, okay...
This sure is getting tense!
Our work gets done alright, but
at this rate, WE won't last!
This kind of a love triangle can't
be taken lightly at all!
I have to do something...
Your cold is getting
worse, isn't it?
I'm fine.
If you say so...
You know, Miyuki... I know that I
can be insensitive sometimes...
...'cause I can't figure certain things out
unless I'm told exactly what's what.
And, I tend to go full speed ahead and
take my best shot, no matter what...
I guess that's why I made
your life hell...
No. Maybe it's ME
who's insensitive.
You see, I don't even know
myself how I feel...
Why do two people
fall in love?
Isn't it because you feel that you
need that certain someone?
But, "need" and "love" aren't
the same thing...
HUH?!
Sorry... I'm acting strange...
Miyuki!
Alright!
Uh-oh, the cops!
He's making a run for it!
He's probably laughing because
this is just a mini-patrol car.
We won't let him get away!
Natsumi!
Let me!
Hey! Scram!
Whew! Instant reaction! ...- SAFE! ...-
Such a close call!
Thanks, Natsumi.
Don't mention it.
Kobayakawa...
Thanks... Nakajima...
I'm not feeling
well today...
Oh, my! They're totally trashed! And this
was a new pair I just got issued!
I'll go after that punk! You guys
take it easy for now. Adios!
Huh? HUH?!
Why are you taking over for us at
a time like this? You moron!
It's okay.
Nakajima needs
to be like that...
Japanese Word Processor           A4 Paper Size         40 Lines
Schedule Proposal
Recently, we've suffered the undesirable
consequences of a non-trivial situation.
I'm sure that both of you know
all too well what's causing it.
And so, as your chief, I must
officially inform you that...
...you, Miyuki Kobayakawa,
and you, Ken Nakajima...
...in the hopes that you will
regain your friendship...
...are hereby ordered to go
on a date this weekend!
Here is your itinerary.
Schedule Proposal
Here I schedule the date of Miss Kobayakawa and Mr. Nakajimain order to resolve their issues.
Date and Time: Sunday, this weekend
Meet in front of Kinshicho Station
Watch the movie "Gone with the Wind" at Kinshicho Shochiku
Shopping at a department store
Dinner at the restaurant "Tobira"
I expect you to scrutinize it carefully
and follow it as exactly as possible!
Yes, sir!
"Meet her by the Kinshicho train
station, at 3 PM..."
Nakajima...
Kobayakawa... I hope
this works out for us!
M... Me too...
Bill to: Bokuto Police Station
Uh... uh... next is
Kinshi Park...
Ostrich 1 to all officers; the subjects are
heading towards the final destination!
They are behaving informally. Date is
proceeding according to plan. Over!
Roger! Natsumi? Yoriko?
Did you get that?
Roger! And now, we
get to see the finale!
They've just passed "Checkpoint
Charlie!" Over!
Confirmed sighting of the subjects!
I shall continue the stakeout.
I feel bad, making you hang out with me
all day, when you've just been sick...
You shouldn't, because I'm
perfectly fine now.
Oh, yeah!
I've washed it for
you. Thanks!
I... 'cause Tsujimoto told me... NO!
I mean, I wanted you to have this!
YES! Good going! "Love
Shall Flourish!"
"Traffic Safety?"
WHAT?!
We're in the traffic safety
department, after all!
Even though we were ordered to be
here, I'm happy that this happened.
Me, too.
Thank you, Nakajima.
Don't you wanna peek?
It's looking good!
Oh, well...
We've just been notified of a car crash
in front of the train station.
Everyone, abort the current operation
and head over to the scene. Over.
Roger!
Time for work!
Okay, let's go!
Wait, Nakajima!
After the rain, scattered diamonds come.
Natsumi! You're over there, aren't you?
C'mon, let's get going!
S... Sure!
Right! Yoriko, you take care of the stuff!
We'll be crossing bridges of rainbows...
It was just getting good!
... nonstop, no matter what we face.
Yahoo! Well... we just happened
to be walking nearby, and...
I don't like chicken-hearted softies... You're Under Arrest!
Next time... ask me out without the
plan and without the entourage!
I love the smile you always have.
With all the passion I have...
... I will protect you from sighs.
The sunset skyline flashes past
in my side-view mirror.
This is the road I drive on every day,
believing in my dreams.
On rainy days, windy days, and days
when I wanted to throw it all away...
... you smiled as you
sat beside me.
I love the unchanging vista, the sky
that we watch together.
That's why I'm confident that I can
hang in there, if it's for you.
I love the smile you always have.
With all the passion I have...
... I will protect you from sighs.
I love this town where we
happened to meet...
And Speaking of Our Heroines...
Natsumi, it was a short year being your
partner and all, but it was great fun!
I'll never forget you!
Huh? Miyuki, you make it
sound like a farewell.
Natsumi! Don't go! Waah!
"Go?!" Where to?!
Tsujimoto! It won't be the
same without you!
Take care! Here's a going-away present!
All of us at Bokuto Police Station
are proud of you guys.
We look forward to seeing you triumph
in your future endeavors!
See you again in You're Under Arrest,
File 4, "On The Road, Again."
Natsumi! It's our last assignment!
Oh, I don't know what's going on,
but I'll take my best shot at it!